<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.130.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:45:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Working Notes</title>
      <link>/posts/working-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:45:54 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/working-notes/</guid>
      <description>Writing help An outline of what ideas you want to expand and write about is great for staying on task while writing in general. I use the word &amp;ldquo;expand&amp;rdquo; to emphasize not just having a lot to talk about but having in depth ideas to expand upon through a structured outline.
Outline theme and plan For this outline I will try not to erase anything so that I will have many ideas to bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog Practice</title>
      <link>/posts/blog-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:42:27 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/blog-practice/</guid>
      <description>Hook Today is a practice shot for my blog post. my topic today will be on writing for self improvement. My purpose for today today is to write sample text to help me work on building system for writing blog posts efficiently and quickly. purpose of writing a blog is to see if it will be profitable as an additive to my current main income. without further rambling let us start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My idea to make money </title>
      <link>/posts/moneymaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/moneymaking/</guid>
      <description>incomplete Money Making The gist of my money making idea is to make a gaming party bus. This idea was inspired the idea of PCI Passthrough and virtual machine software. I would use server hardware fast enough to run 4 gaming computers at once then have 4 of those servers so I can host 16 gaming players at once.
The 16 players would remotely connect to the server through a LAN wifi connection on a gaming steam deck device that does not run the software directly but uses the steam deck as a screen and controller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Journal 1</title>
      <link>/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>#Family #Careers #experience #blogging incomplete See [[My-notes]]
My Family Life before I got married I was living with my parents
My career Today I wanted to relay my current and first corporate work experience. First thing I wanted to say is that I absolutely love my job, my current job is to watch heart rhythms and notify a nurse if there heart changes in condition.
My work in my words My work is similar to a call center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public notes for blog</title>
      <link>/posts/my-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/my-notes/</guid>
      <description>incomplete #Tasks #Outline
Gabriel Murray&amp;rsquo;s blog this will be my first blog that is public
I have a few things to do to make this website public but for now I want to just get it out there on the internet
things that i need to do are in no particular order
connect my domain to my website Customize theme for website figure out hugo&amp;rsquo;s footer and header options figure out what the blog will be about make a section for personal items make a section for coding make a section for progres reports and reflections make a section for life events such as general conference make a section for professional life events such as new job make a blog post join exsiting note daily from personal notes starting from the oldest [[First-Post]] #Tasks #Outline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/resume-coverletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/resume-coverletter/</guid>
      <description>Non-IT Roles Banner Health Cardiac Monitor Technician Relays messages about cardiac (heart rhythm) changes in a timely manner to the Registered Nurse (RN) via phone line Make Staff Assignments for Tech stations Notify Certified Nurse Assistant (CNA) of heart detection device issues. Lights By Troy Putting up the Christmas Lights Taking constructive criticism when light installation is not up to company standards Talking to residents for approval IT-Related Roles Student / High School Cisco Packet Tracer Setup and test networking and IT setups for reliability and testing in a virtual environment ability to use managed switches and other technologies and services in a enclosed virtual &amp;ldquo;fake environment&amp;rdquo; Basic Cyber Security and server software Setting up basic IT best practices for windows and Linux for security systems Example: Group Policy Editor in Microsoft Windows &amp;ldquo;Hidden Settings&amp;rdquo; Example: Setting up sudo configurations in Linux Example: ssh configurations files for security Past Home Projects Relating to IT Setting up a Email Server using scripts from Internet Setting up Docker Services Example Web Server Home Lab Local Self Hosted AI using Docker Setting up Arch Linux Alpine Linux Debian and Red hat Linux derivatives Experience with editing Windows setup settings / configuration Example: Preinstalled Software / .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
